In this game,
if you say someone's
name,
they teleport next to
you.
First to the top
of the tower wins
a million coins.
Leo is one jump
from the top.
Max at the bottom,
Leo.
Pop Leo's back at
the bottom.
Max climbs.
Leo yells.
Max pop.
Up.
Leo.
Down.
Up.
Max down.
So Leo changes his
name tag to Steve.
Leo nothing.
He's climbing.
Max squints at the
tag.
Steve pop.
Mia steps out onto
a ledge over the
lava.
Turns around and says
sweetly.
Max.
Pop pop.
They appear next to
her.
In mid -air.
Straight into the lava.
Now it's Mia against
one noob.
Three steps from the
top.
Easy.
She reads his name
tag.
X underscore dark shadow
dragon slayer underscore X
X TWO THOUSAND.
And the noob jumps.
Nine.
Pop.
He appears next to
her,
holding a million coins.
Follow ViralRobloxGames for
more stories like this.